boardofwisdom.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement covers the site WWW.BOARDOFWISDOM.COM. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users' privacy, we are disclosing our information practices. This document describes: 

  1. 1\. What personally identifiable information THE BOARD OF WISDOM collects.
  2. 2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  3. 3\. What organization collects the information.
  4. 4\. How THE BOARD OF WISDOM uses the information.
  5. 5\. With whom THE BOARD OF WISDOM may share user information.
  6. 6.What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  7. 7\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under THE BOARD OF WISDOM control.
  8. 8\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Art Schrage by email at webmaster@boardofwisdom.com. 

Information Collection and Use

**Information Collection**

THE BOARD OF WISDOM is the sole owner of the information collected on WWW.BOARDOFWISDOM.COM. THE BOARD OF WISDOM collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

**Registration**

In order to use the personalized features of this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to provide a valid email address. We use this information to contact the users about services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as location and zip code). 

**Order**

All ordering on this site is currently done through third party fulfillment services such as Amazon.com. For privacy information about these vendors, please visit their websites. 

**Information Use**

We gather data volunteered by users through the registration form, online suggestion form, and other forms. We also track usage of website features such as "favorites" and content emailing. We review usage totals in various categories periodically. We use this data to adjust the site's content to better serve our visitors' interests. 

**Profile**

We do not profile our users beyond the information normally required in the registration form. We monitor server log files in aggregate, but do not tie that data to specific visitors to create usage profiles. We do not share your profile with third parties. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. [Provide a link to information on cookies.] 

For our site, the cookie contains information such as your username and whether you are logged in. Cookies are used to provide convenience for the user, not to gather information. By setting a cookie on our site, users do not have to log in with a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by various affiliate programs including but not limited to amazon.com, directleads.com, linkshare.com, and cj.com. Information about users' visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about our third party advertisers, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please visit the websites listed above. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by WWW.BOARDOFWISDOM.COM only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use this data to analyze trends, administer the site, track page usage, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a free tracking utility called Analog that summarizes aggregate user movement on the site. 

Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We do not use Clear Gifs, Web Beacons, or Web Bugs. 

Communications from the Site

**Special Offers and Updates**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, or special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

Sharing

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

We may in the future share aggregated demographic information with certain partners and advertisers. This will not include or be linked to any personally identifiable information. 

**Business Transitions**

In the event THE BOARD OF WISDOM goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email and a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users will be given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form will have an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking the unsubscribe link in our email communication. We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the edit profile page or the user may contact us at webmaster@boardofwisdom.com to opt-out. 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, THE BOARD OF WISDOM, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Surveys [ & Contests]**

[From time-to-time] our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used [shared with the contest [survey] sponsors] to notify the winners and award prizes. [Anonymous] Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our emailing services for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's email address. THE BOARD OF WISDOM will not send the friend any email outside that requested by the user or the friend. 

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. Our registration/order forms purposely do not ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number). 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to webmaster@boardofwisdom.com. 

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the edit profile page or by emailing webmaster@boardofwisdom.com. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, on the homepage and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

webmaster@boardofwisdom.com  
Board of Wisdom  
310 Grant Street, Suite 2310  
Pittsburgh, PA 15219
